It's made
me want
to learn
more.
It's not made me just want to stop there.
It's made me want to progress my career.
It's very manageable.
Nothing to be scared of at all.
It's confidence, and it's an optimism that I now have.
I've enjoyed working at home, at my own pace.
Really, really got me thinking.
Over the moon. I was completely overjoyed.
It's given me confidence to go on and study
and hopefully lead to me gaining a degree.
I think it's one of the best things I've done really.
I felt quite elated
that I'd actually taken that step and done it.
It's just a feeling of having tried something new
and succeeded.
On top of the world.
And I can't wait to do the next course.
I have really, really enjoyed it.
And it's given me a thirst for knowledge
and I want to carry on doing it.